National Council On Household Employment Records 5226
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI. MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPTS
  - Alsop, Natalie. no title (Box 6, Folder 69)
    Several pages re demestic workers
  - Barber, Edith. (Box 6, Folder 70)
    Includes chapter outline, questionnaire & introduction. No date
  - Magnus, Erma. Coverage of Domestic Workers by Social Insurance, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    114 p and tables
  - "Negro Domestic Workers in Private Homes In Baltimore. " (Box 6, Folder 72)
    18 p transcript
  - It's Fun to Work In A Home. I Really Mean It. (Box 6, Folder 73)
    Author unknown, no date. 7 p
  - Progress in the Field of Employer-Employee Relationships in the Home (Box 6, Folder 74)
    Author unknown, no date. 9 p
  - The Extent and Types of Domestic Service (Box 6, Folder 75)
    Author unknown
- Images digitized from the collection. (Box 7)